pickrice.com 2012-02-01

# PickRice- Global Online Shopping for Cell phones, Electronics, Clothing, Free Shipping

  *     *  Personal Information Collects
    * PickRice respects your privacy and takes your online safety seriously. In order to provide you with the best products, efficient customer service, and timely updates, we record a variety of information from your visit to our site. To better protect y...
  *     *  Use Personal Information
    * How does PickRice.com use your personal information? Help make this site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once. Help you quickly find information, products, and services. Help us create content on this Site that i...
  *     *  Secure Information Collected
    * How does PickRice.com secure information collected about me? Safeguarding all financial transactions done through this Site with Secure Sockets Layer ("SSL") encryption. Granting only employees who are providing a specific service access ...
  *     *  What choices do I have?
    * What choices do I have regarding PickRice.com’s collection of my information? You can choose to: Correct or update your personal information Stop receiving mail to your email address Disable your account to prevent any future purchases th...
  *     *  Use and Disclose Information
    * How does PickRice.com use and disclose information collected from me offline? As PickRice.com collects most information through our Site, this Privacy Policy applies only to online collection of personal information. We also protect all personal in...
  *     *  Where can I find updates to this policy?
    * Where can I find updates to this policy? To keep you informed of what information we collect, use, and disclose, we will post any changes or updates to this Privacy Notice on this Site and encourage you to review this Privacy Notice from time to tim...
